VERONICA SOLANGE CAPOBIANCO

FrontEnd Developer

https://github.com/veritocapito



Since 2020 complementing my career as a professional accountant with web programming. Responsible, committed and determined. I believe in constant training and new challenges. I have worked on projects with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular, Java, Springboot.

In my career I have assumed high levels of responsibility and acquired interpersonal skills. I bring value in the implementation of IT systems and technology solutions.

I am looking for my first experience in IT, as a FrontEnd developer.

EDUCATION



ORACLE NEXT EDUCATION - ALURA LATAM

Front End Programming. JAVASCRIPT. REACT. mar. 2023 - sep. 2023



WORKERTECH - PLUGIT - ADA ITW

Front End Programming. HTML. CSS. Maquetación. may. 2023 - sep. 2023



MINHUB

Front End Programming. JAVASCRIPT. feb. 2023 - mar. 2023



Open Bootcamp

PATH 0 to DEV, HTML. CSS. JAVASCRIPT. ANGULAR. JAVA. jul. 2022 - dic. 2022



Argentina Programa

#YoProgramo, Full Stack Web Programming. Angular. JAVA.
jun. 2022 - feb. 2023



Centro de e-Learning UTN FRBA.

Full Stack Developer, Web Programming. jun. 2020 - dic. 2021.



Argentina Programa

#SeProgramar, Full Stack Web Programming. ago. 2021 - oct. 2021.

Contadora Publica Nacional

Universidad de Flores https://www.uflo.edu.ar

University of Management, 2009 - 2013 GRADUATED with GPA: 8.70 - Enrolled in C.P.C.C.E.C.A.B.A.

High School Graduate Commercial Expert

Escuela Nacional de Comercio № 32 Dr. José Leon Suárez, 1994 - 1998

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NO COUNTRY https://www.nocountry.tech/ Noviembre 2022 - Diciembre 2022 FRONTEND Developer.

I am part of the development team for the implementation of a medical clinic shift manager. Technologies: Angular / Javascritp.

<u>Estudio CAPOBIANCO</u> <u>www.estudiocapobianco.com.ar</u> <u>Julio 2016 - Presente</u> <u>Public Accountant, owner.</u>

Accounting Firm. Taxes. Payroll.

Accounting Software: Bejerman/Onvio Systems.

Implementation of systems.

Estudio Blasco www.blasco.com.ar Junio 2011 - Presente

Payroll Manager, freelance.

Inherent tasks. Personnel in charge.

Accounting Software: Bejerman Systems. System implementation.

Implementation of systems.

IDIOMS English Certificate Level C1 = https://www.efset.org/cert/r6fuPk

TECHNOLOGIES | HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript | Python | Java | MySQL | TypeScript | Angular | React | Git | GitHub | npm | SpringBoot |

Windows | Microsoft Office | ERP: SISTEMAS BEJERMAN | ONVIO | TANGO SOFTWARE |

SOFT SKILLS Communication | Leadership | Adaptability | Teamwork | Proactivity | Organization | Responsibility | Continuous learning |

INTERESES Music. Sports.

REFERENCES - Cr. Sergio Blasco (Estudio Blasco)

Cel. (11) 15 4478-2272 sergio@blasco.com.ar